Professor Celia,
It's been three days since I left Beltrant,
the royal capital.
Year 996 of the Holy Era, Summer
I've safely reached a neighboring kingdom,
and arrived in Amande, a market
town in the Kingdom of Galarc.
Kingdom of Galarc, Amande Market Town
Not here... right?
As there were wanted posters
circulating in the royal capital,
it was difficult to procure the
items I needed for my journey,
but they haven't reached this town yet,
so please don't worry about me.
Amande is a bustling, lively town.
Foodstuffs are plentiful,
and it looks like I'll be able to acquire
preserved foods quickly, which is a relief.
I guess I'm a little too on edge.
Seirei Gensouki
The Assassin Girl
Welcome!
We have soup-style pasta!
One bowl for eight lesser coppers!
Did you say... pasta?
Huh? Son, is this your
first time in this town?
Uh, yes.
Soup-style pasta! Lady Liselotte,
the one who governs Amande,
invented something out of wheat called
"noodles," and this dish uses those.
Liselotte...
This is the finished dish.
Thanks for waiting!
Pasta...
It's the first time I've
seen it in this world.
And I heard the word "noodles," too.
Looks good, right?
And it really is good, too!
Then, can I have one bowl, please?
Thanks for the business!
It's delicious!
Right?
It's a nostalgic flavor.
Could it be that this Liselotte person
also came from the same world as Haruto?
Not that it matters at this point.
Thinking about that stuff doesn't mean
there's anything that can be done about it.
When you're bigger, I'll take you there.
It's a place called Yagumo.
Really? You promised, okay?
I...
I want to see the place my
mother and father came from.
It was a promise I made with my mother.
Is that it?
You want to buy noodles?
Yes. I think they'll be good
to take on my journey.
Oh, and this was delicious.
In that case, try heading down that
way to the Ricca merchant guild.
There should be a long line to the
menjuu shop on the first floor,
so I'm sure you'll recognize it right away.
Did you say... menjuu?
Yeah! It's another thing
that Lady Liselotte...
It's yummy, isn't it?
Yeah!
Two meat menjuu and one cheese menjuu!
Thank you for waiting!
They're hot, so please be careful.
Manjuu meat buns?
That feels nostalgic, somehow.
Hello. Welcome to the Ricca merchant guild.
Thank you very much.
We hope you'll come again soon.
Sir?
We ask that you refrain from
wearing a sword within the store.
You can check your things, and we can
look after them for you if you'd like.
Oh, thank you.
Black hair?
If you would, please.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I will be helping you today.
My name is Lotte.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Thank you for waiting.
Fifteen kilos of dried pasta
and ten kilos of barley.
I've also readied cooking
implements and seasonings.
Have you? Thank you very much.
I added a large rucksack,
but it's all very heavy.
Will you be all right carrying it home?
Please, have some.
Thank you.
I may not look it, but I've done a lot of
physical training. Please, don't worry.
Are you accustomed to drinking black tea?
Among my acquaintances is
a lady who loves black tea.
As I drank it with her, I learned a lot.
In that case, could it be that you
recognize what those tea leaves are?
This unique aroma and slight astringency...
Are these leaves from Lis?
You use very good tea here.
And this teaware, too.
In order to have the best possible
dealings with our customers,
the environment for the negotiations
must be as perfect as possible.
That's our merchant guild's motto!
Then... may we undertake the
delivery of a letter for you?
Yes.
And so, I've successfully completed
my purchases, and I'm about to set out.
Once I leave the Strahl region,
I won't be able to send more letters,
but please don't worry.
No news of me is proof that I am doing well.
I'm off.
Haruto.
Take care.
Thank you for all your help.
That boy was a bit mysterious,
wasn't he, Lady Liselotte?
I'm Lotte right now, Cosette.
So you are.
A child?
Hey, are you all right?
Poison?
A beast person?
I will...
kill you.
I have to neutralize the poison, or else...
I'm sorry. I can't let you kill me.
The poison didn't work?
She's fast!
Enchant Physical Ability!
She hadn't already enhanced her
physical abilities with magic?
But that movement...
How fast will she be after enhancing?
Why... Why is this person...
He's human. Why is he so fast?
She's too focused on the knife.
This is as far as it goes.
You understand me, right?
N-No... No!
I don't want to die!
H-Hey! Calm down!
H-Help me! Mom!
Mama!
I suppose I have no choice.
A Collar of Submission?
The magic in that book...
Dispell, was it?
If I imitate that, will this come off?
Hey, Latifa! Wake up!
Latifa...
Latifa?
I'm Endo Suzune.
Are you still half-asleep?
Latifa...
What am I to you?
I am your esteemed older brother, Stewart.
Come on, say, "my esteemed older brother"!
I-I don't want—
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
"Esteemed older brother." Say it!
E-Esteemed older brother...
Hey. Wake up.
Stop that. Your hands and legs are bound.
It seems you understand the situation.
If you don't want to die,
don't get violent like you did earlier.
If I don't fight, then you won't kill me?
That depends on you.
Did you come here from Beltrant?
Then...
Do you know what this is?
A... collar?
It's... gone!
Why?
This collar was the reason
you were obeying orders, right?
You won't be stricken with pain any more.
Since the collar is gone, you won't have
any problems answering my questions, right?
Who gave you your orders?
You and I are the only
ones here. Don't worry.
I-I don't know my master's name.
I've never been told, so...
You don't even know the name of their house?
The name of the house?
B-But I do know the name of
my esteemed older brother!
He said it was Stewart!
Stewart... Is he a beast person, like you?
My older brother is human.
The human who trained me.
Human...
Then, it must be him.
It's that commoner who's responsible!
Fearing that the truth may come to light,
Duke Huguenot decided to make me disappear.
Thinking about it that way,
everything seems consistent, but...
Are there others besides
you trying to kill me?
I don't know.
But I don't think so... probably.
Then,
here is my final question.
All right.
Do you still intend to kill me?
I won't k-kill you!
Do as you like, then.
I've left all your equipment
with that robe over there.
It means you're free to run away.
Since the collar that controlled you is gone,
there's no need for you
to go back to your master.
But here in Strahl, where
beast people are made slaves,
there is nowhere safe for this girl.
If you leave this kingdom
and head to the east,
there is a vast area known as the Wilderness.
Somewhere in that place,
there is a land where beast people like
you and other demi-humans live together.
The Wilderness? East...
The direction I've been traveling.
Instead of staying here,
looking for others of your kind there
might be an easier way for you to live.
Others of my kind. East. Wilderness.
I'll be going, then.
Let me tell you this. The next time
you attack me, I won't show any mercy.
Did you still have some
kind of business with me?
U-Um, east...
I want to go with you.
You seem to have misunderstood.
I didn't release you from your enslavement
because I wanted to rescue you.
It's only that not killing you was
more convenient for me. That's all.
B-But... I don't know what I should do.
You know, I'm human, just like
the people who enslaved you.
Aren't you scared?
You don't feel... bad.
You believe I would think nothing
of you trying to kill me?
I-I'm sorry.
It's not like I'm angry.
You couldn't disobey your
orders is all, right?
But there's no guarantee that
you won't attack me again.
In short, I can't trust you.
Do you understand?
Then, th-this collar! You can put it on me!
I don't mind! So please...
Wh-Why did you bring that?
You hated having that collar on, didn't you?
I hate being alone like this more.
I'm scared.
Please...
All right. Do what you want.
Oh, uh, I will!
Thank you very much!
Get rid of that collar.
Oh!
What's your name?
It's Latifa.
I see.
I'm Rio.
Nice to meet you, Latifa.
Yes, it is!
I-I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize
for something like that.
Here.
I'm allowed to eat that?
Yes. No need to be polite.
It's delicious.
Yeah.
No one's going to steal it from you.
Take your time eating.
My meals... They said it was pet food...
Every day, my older brother would...
We've just about reached the Wilderness.
It's not too hard for you?
I'm fine.
We've already crossed the border, so...
It's a little early, but let's make camp here.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because I'm holding you back.
No, you're not.
Haruto...
It's a letter from Rio!
I'm so glad he seems well.
Reaching Amande in three days...
That's so fast!
Not receiving more news makes
me feel a little lonely, but..
I hope that, wherever you are
on your journey, you are safe.
Wow! Spaghetti?
You know what this is?
Yes! It's spaghetti!
May I eat some?
S-Sure.
Thank you for... the food!
You've eaten pasta before?
Yes!
Oh, um... Yes, I used to eat it. I think.
I see.
I thought you seemed accustomed to eating it.
There's more. Eat as much as you want.
Thank you!
Calling this pasta "spaghetti" means...
Could it be that this girl is also...
What's wrong?
I don't like this! Where am I?
I want to go home.
It's all right. It's not scary anymore.
Mom, Dad, Onii-san...
I want to go home to Tokyo...
Tokyo?!
There really is no mistake.
This girl is also...
Onii-san...
Rest easy. Sleep.
His hair is black.
He does look like him, doesn't he?
Onii-chan...
Good morning. Did you sleep well?
Are you all right?
Yes, Onii...Rio!
Oni Rio?
N-No, that's not what I meant!
I was about to say "Onii-chan," and then...
Rio, would you mind if
I called you O-Onii-chan?
What?
You d-don't want me to?
It's not that I mind, but...
Mom, Dad, Onii-san...
I want to go home to Tokyo...
A girl who was still so young
reincarnated from Earth to
this world and was made a slave.
She must have felt so alone.
If this will comfort her
heart even a little, then...
Onii-chan!
What are we having for breakfast today?
What do you want to eat, Latifa?
I want omelets! With cheese in them!
Omelets, huh? All right.
Say, Latifa?
You really can't see that big
tree over there, can you?
The one you were talking about yesterday?
I can only see regular forest.
Latifa can't see it. That means...
Is it being blocked from people's
awareness through magic?
Onii-chan...
Are we really going in there?
We won't get lost?
We'll be fine.
Onii-chan, it's very faint,
but I smell something I don't recognize.
More than one scent.
Is it different from an animal's scent?
Yes.
Since it's faint, whatever the scent
belongs to isn't nearby, right?
Yes, I think.
In that case, why don't we
rest around here for today?
Our goal may be close by.
Really?
We'll finally be able to leave the forest!
Is she having another nightmare?
With this, she won't have any scary dreams.
What?!
Next Time
Forest of Spirits
"Forest of Spirits."
Spirit Chronicles
Exciting Bonus Manga
That boy
was a bit
mysterious,
wasn't he,
Lady Liselotte?
By Minazuki Futago
I'm
Lotte
right
now,
though.
So
you
are,
Lady
Liselotte!
You're
doing
that
on
purpose...
aren't
you?
Tee-hee